Okay, so how do we get the data out of
that readable stream? Well, we need to
call thejson
function on it or do.json depending on
how you want to say that. Um, I've heard
so many arguments about how to say that,
but here um in my async await because it
is an asynchronous function, we need to
use the keyword await again. So, we
could say let JSON data equal await
response do.json.
JSON
and then we could console.log
the JSON data.
Um down here what we'd need to do is we
would need to instead of console.logging
our result we would need to do res.json
and then we can chain on another then so
it says wait for this to finish then do
this wait for that to finish and then
take the result of that
and console.log log the result. So, if I
save this, we're going to get the same
thing twice.
And so, you can see that we get our slip
object um which has an ID and it says
don't try and bump start a motorcycle on
an icy road. I have no idea what that
means. I'm not a motorcyclist, but um
there you go. There's that piece of
advice. Um and you can see that both
objects came back exactly as we would
expect. Now, I do have to give you a
caveat here. If you prefer this method
of chaining thens together, remember
that if you write a lambda function or
the arrow function as some people like
to call it, if you write it all on one
line, this part is returned by default.
But if you don't write it all on one
line, um let's say you put some curly
braces around this, then you have to use
the return keyword. So I'm going to
format my code. So let's say you wrote
your code like this. So you fetch and
then inside of your then you do your
res.json. If we do that and we come
over, we can see that the first code,
the async await code still works and we
get our object printed out. But here it
prints out undefined. And why is that?
Well, because this then was taking the
result of this then's return. And this
then didn't boy, that's a tongue twister
right there. This didn't return
anything. So because it didn't return
anything, we tried to take in the result
of what it returned and log it, but it
didn't return anything. So if you want
to write it on multiple lines then you
need to type return res.json and then
you will go back to having your code
work as expected. Just wanted to give
you that caveat. If you broke it onto
multiple lines, you will need to use the
return keyword.